Turn on hob
Open fridge
Grab sauce pan
Close fridge
Open lid
Close lid and
Put sauce pan down
Turn sauce pan
Turn lid
Grab sauce pan
Put sauce pan on hob
Open cupboard
Grab rice
put rice
open container
open rice bag
pour rice
pick up glass
place glass
shake container
close container
pick up rice
put rice in cupboard
close cupboard
pick up crisps
place crisps
close cupboard
pick up broom
place broom
move clothes
pick up broom
sweep floor
continue sweeping floor
pick up glass
place glass
sweep floor
continue sweeping floor
put broom
pick up dustpan and brush
sweep floor
continue sweeping floor
pour dust pan in bin
put dustpan and brush down
[END SUBTITLE]